Born to aristocracy. Bred for idiocy.
Fackham Hall is a comedy, history film directed by Jim O'Hanlon.
A new porter embarks on an unlikely relationship with the
youngest daughter of a prominent English family.
Simultaneously, rivalries are spilling over in the Davenport family, led by the Lord and Lady as they also
weather the epic failure of the wedding of their eldest daughter to her caddish cousin.
Rose Davenport, played by Thomasin McKenzie.
Eric Noone, played by Ben Radcliffe.
Poppy Davenport, played by Emma Laird.
Lord Davenport, played by Damian Lewis.
Lady Davenport, played by Katherine Waterston.
Phyllis Davenport, played by Lizzie Hopley.
Fackham Hall is a 2025 period slapstick comedy parody film directed by Jim O'Hanlon
and co-written by Jimmy Carr, Patrick Carr, and The Dawson Brothers.
The film stars Thomasin McKenzie, Ben Radcliffe, Katherine Waterston, Emma Laird, Tom
Goodman-Hill, Anna Maxwell Martin, Sue Johnston, Tom Felton, and Damian Lewis.
Fackham Hall was released in the United States by Bleecker Street on December 5, 2025, and in
the United Kingdom by Entertainment Film Distributors on December 12, 2025.
The film explores themes of social satire,
historical comedy, witty, hilarious, amused.
The tone is lighthearted.